{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728603614","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728603614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lina_lina-ndoo-yake"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lina"," userResponse":" lina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728612814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728612814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_tano-hana-taji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728622642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728622642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jona_jona-yenu-kinu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jona"," userResponse":" jona"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728634260","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728634260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lina_lina-lako-moto"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lina"," userResponse":" lina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728643423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728643423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_huku-yuko-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728653433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728653432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kina_kina-juma-kwao"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kina"," userResponse":" kina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728663407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728663407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuna"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728675088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728675088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aina_kale-lini-aina"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aina"," userResponse":" aina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728684954","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728684954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pana_damu-pana-babu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pana"," userResponse":" pana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728694001","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728694001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_adie-joto-tuna"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728699768","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728699765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_adie-joto-tuna"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728707334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728707333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_adie-joto-tuna"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728712874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728712873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" a3248170-c8e3-42a2-9406-8780772e92ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_adie-joto-tuna"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728744385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728744385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728746864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728746864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728757297","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728757297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728760022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728760022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728768783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728768782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728770193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728770192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728780076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728780076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728782315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728782315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728792580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728792580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728799200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728799200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728801683","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728801683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728813995","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728813995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728817076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728817076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728825185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728825185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728826622","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728826622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728837700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728837700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728840268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728840267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728849357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728849357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728856289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728856289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728858928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728858928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728869248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728869247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728870880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728870880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728876925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728876925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728887844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728887843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 2eefdabb-6208-479d-acda-84b737a6d28a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728893918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728893917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 9866d771-e1f2-4a88-9dcf-89dc91693b27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728909539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728909538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 9866d771-e1f2-4a88-9dcf-89dc91693b27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728912203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728912202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 9866d771-e1f2-4a88-9dcf-89dc91693b27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728912332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728912332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 9866d771-e1f2-4a88-9dcf-89dc91693b27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728924073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728924073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mukhwana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUKHWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728925121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728925121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mukhwana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUKHWANA"," userResponse":" MUKHWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728928956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728928956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728930000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728930000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728933086","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728933086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728934124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728934124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWANA"," userResponse":" HAWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728938207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728938207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutokana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728939255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728939255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutokana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKANA"," userResponse":" KUTOKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728942716","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728942716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728943753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728943753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINA"," userResponse":" SHINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728947039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728947039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuvuna"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728948074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728948073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuvuna"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUNA"," userResponse":" KUVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728951472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728951472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728951781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728951781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728952639","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728952639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITANA"," userResponse":" ALIITANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728954395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728954395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728954523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728954523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" aliitana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728954670","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728954670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 546bf9dd-0a30-4280-824a-29e5191e8626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728967613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728967612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mukhwana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUKHWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728968659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728968658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mukhwana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUKHWANA"," userResponse":" MUKHWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728973248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728973247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728974286","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728974286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728978134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728978134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728979202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728979202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWANA"," userResponse":" HAWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728982411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728982411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipomwona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728983461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728983460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipomwona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728993746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728993745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutokana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKANA"," userResponse":" KUTOKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728994798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728994798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutokana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKANA"," userResponse":" KUTOKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728998804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728998803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINA"," userResponse":" SHINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549728999869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549728999868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINA"," userResponse":" SHINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729003074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729003074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuvuna"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUNA"," userResponse":" KUVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729004117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729004117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuvuna"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUNA"," userResponse":" KUVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729007522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729007521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729008575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729008575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729014770","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729014769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729015799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729015799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729019676","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729019676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729019830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729019830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729025381","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729025381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729032821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729032820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729040268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729040268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729048366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729048366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729057507","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729057507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 684b1b5e-2573-4ddd-8d16-7e8f315ba9aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729072021","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729072021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_titi-bata-uani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729083121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729083121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lini_mali-taya-lini"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lini"," userResponse":" lini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729099609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729099609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_ruka-kata-nini"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729109229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729109229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_tani-wawe-koti"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729121340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729121340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pini_kaka-bado-pini"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pini"," userResponse":" pini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729130539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729130539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_honi_duma-honi-hewa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" honi"," userResponse":" honi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729139455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729139455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_hawa-ziwa-tani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729150530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729150530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_kuni-pili-mali"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuni"," userResponse":" kuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729158821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729158821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_uani-yote-tuna"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729167360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729167360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729173105","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729173104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729183005","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729183004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729190831","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729190831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729200089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729200089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729208082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729208081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729217004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729217004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729223856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729223855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729230963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729230963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729238517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729238517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729247561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729247561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729256615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729256615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729264486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729264486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729272338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729272337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729286725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729286724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729294610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729294610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729302138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729302138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 0faeb671-d793-4370-91bd-c44bcc48242f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729318208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729318208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_ruka-kata-nini"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729330227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729330227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_titi-bata-uani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729410448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729410448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pini_kaka-bado-pini"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pini"," userResponse":" pini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729418613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729418613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" raha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729431311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729431310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729440760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729440760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_tani-wawe-koti"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729451813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729451813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_honi_duma-honi-hewa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" honi"," userResponse":" honi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729461840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729461839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_uani-yote-tuna"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729472464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729472464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_hawa-ziwa-tani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729483884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729483884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lini_mali-taya-lini"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lini"," userResponse":" lini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729493186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729493186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_kuni-pili-mali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuni"," userResponse":" mali"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729502747","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729502747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_kuni-pili-mali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuni"," userResponse":" kuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729508535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729508535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_kuni-pili-mali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729516080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729516080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 5d061f96-b3a4-4b3b-bfa1-cf8e51862b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_kuni-pili-mali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729526600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729526599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" MFUKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729530796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729530796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729532355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729532355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729535671","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729535671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729537243","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729537243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanzoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729541592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729541592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanzoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729543157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729543156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" geni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" GENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729545516","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729545516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" geni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729545635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729545635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" ca848c8d-f37f-4393-9f14-3a4ad9589e13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" geni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" GENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729557742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729557742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" MFUKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729563282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729563282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729564819","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729564819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729568816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729568816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729570379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729570379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanzoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729574204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729574204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanzoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729575793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729575793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729580081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729580081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729581673","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729581673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" geni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" GENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729585582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729585582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" geni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729587143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729587143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729591229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729591229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729592849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729592848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729596420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729596419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729598024","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729598023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729602354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729602353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729603942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729603942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gizani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZANI"," userResponse":" GIZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729608435","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729608435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gizani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729610018","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729610018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOKENI"," userResponse":" TOKENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729614795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729614795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOKENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729616803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729616803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729616985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729616985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOKENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729622262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729622261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729631003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729631002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729636938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729636938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 84c47ce3-8e02-471f-91c6-805b02aae40e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729637013","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729637013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8207c0d4-f756-4c8f-970f-d5f931f0f557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729643248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729643247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8207c0d4-f756-4c8f-970f-d5f931f0f557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729648965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729648964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8207c0d4-f756-4c8f-970f-d5f931f0f557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729663248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729663248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_tani-lala-vuta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729671162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729671162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_geni_geni-kumi-jike"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" geni"," userResponse":" geni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729682006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729682006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_pana-nani-lori"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729692772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729692772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_jani-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729703448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729703448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_yadi-jani-maua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729712618","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729712618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_neno-yetu-jani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729721551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729721551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_mara-nani-tele"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729731723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729731722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pini_jitu-pini-isha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pini"," userResponse":" pini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729744736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729744736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_elsa-kuni-mbao"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuni"," userResponse":" kuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729754158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729754158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729759955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729759955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729776892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729776891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729783726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729783726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729802793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729802793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_190942"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}